I need a place to hide.
Mi serve un posto dove nascondermi.
I'm a blood mage.
Sono un mago blood.
I-  I can't move!
Non... Non riesco a muovermi!
What have you done to me?
Cosa mi avete fatto?
You drinks the blood.
Bere il sangue...
You likes the blood.
Piacere il sangue...
Makes you strong.
Sangue rendere forte.
(whimpers)
(piagnucolio)
I wouldn't eat him.
Fossi in voi non lo mangerei.
You don't know where he's been.
Non sapete neanche dov'è stato.
You'll be able to move in a moment.
Tra un attimo potrai muoverti.
Whatever they did...
Qualunque cosa mi abbiano fatto...
It's already wearing off.
Sta già perdendo efficacia.
Thank you.
Grazie.
I mean, if you hadn't come then-
Nel senso, se non fosse stato per te...
Yeah, yeah.
Certo, certo.
Arianne.
Arianne.
Uh, Jered.
Ehm, Jered.
So... Jered.
Senti... Jered.
Where are you sleeping tonight?
Dove hai intenzione di dormire stanotte?
Morning.
'Giorno.
So.
Dunque.
What do you think?
Che ne pensi?
Well, he's pleased to see you.
Beh, è contento di vederti.
I'm still not sure about this, Ari. We only need to miss one-
Non ne sono completamente certa, Ari. Abbiamo solo un'opportunità...
Oh, sleeping beauty's up.
Oh, il bello addormentato è sveglio.
Then we won't miss anything.
Allora non sbaglieremo.
Lanni's that good.
Lanni è molto abile.
Nice to be wanted.
È bello sentirsi desiderata.
Aww, she's so hard to please.
Ah, com'è difficile farla contenta...
Unlike some.
A differenza di altri.
And so, we can take care of the walking guardians, which just leaves-
Allora possiamo occuparci dei guardiani, perciò resta solo--
(coughs)
(si schiarisce la voce)
Where are my clothes?
Dove sono i miei vestiti?
I don't know, I wasn't paying much attention.
Non ne ho idea, non ero molto attenta.
I think that's his jerkin on the wardrode, there.
Penso che quello sul guardaroba sia il suo giustacuore.
Ah.
Ah.
Erm...
Ehm...
Do you think you could get it for me?
Ti spiace passarmelo?
Oh, I couldn't. Another woman's wardrobe.
No, non mi permetterei mai. È il guardaroba di un'altra donna.
I can't reach up there.
Io non ci arrivo.
I'll tell you what, love.
Ti dico io cosa facciamo, bello.
Why don't we give you some new clothes?
Perché non ti cambi quei vestiti?
I'm really not sure about this.
Non ne sono proprio sicuro.
You'll be fine.
Tranquillo.
All you have to do is get us through Karak's front door.
Basta che tu ci faccia oltrepassare la porta principale di Karak.
That's it.
Nient'altro.
But I need to find the Blooded.
Ma devo trovare i Blood.
Well, you've found them.
Beh, li hai trovati.
And the Blooded are going to Karak's tower.
E i Blood vanno alla torre di Karak.
But-
Ma--
We're here.
Ci siamo.
You'll be fine.
Andrà tutto bene.
Just be confident.
Abbi fiducia in te.
He lives down there?
Vive in quel vicolo?
Obvious blood mage...
Mago blood appariscente...
Dead blood mage.
Mago blood morto.
Remember - blood mages are always obsessed with their potency.
Ricorda, i maghi blood sono ossessionati dalla loro potenza.
It'll keep his mind off things.
Gli terrà la mente occupata.
Can I help you, sir?
Posso aiutarla, signore?
Urm...
Ehm...
I am... the blood mage, Jered.
Sono... Un mago blood, Jered.
Uh, th-th-the great and... mighty blood... mage... Jered, and I, uh, seek...
Ehm, il g-g-rande e... poderoso mago... blood...  Jered, e vorrei...
Ah, I DEMAND that you let me into this... hovel, immediately!
Cioè, ESIGO che mi lasci entrare in questa... topaia, immediatamente!
Um.
Ecco.
Mmm hmm.
Hm... Hm...
And why exactly is that, sir?
È perché dovrei, signore?
Well.  Good question.
Beh... Buona domanda.
I, er...  Well, I wish to give the - your - master the...
Beh... Ehm... Io vorrei porre al servizio del... del tuo padrone...
...benefit of my superior magical wisdom and knowledge in the field of, uh...
La mia superiore esperienza magica e la mia conoscenza nel campo della, ehm...
Magic.
Magia.
And things.
E altre cose.
Ah, I see.
Ah, capisco.
Well, since you are a mage of power...
Beh, dato che è un mago molto potente...
You will have no problems with passing through the portal.
Non avrà problemi ad attraversare il portale.
Is that right, sir.
Giusto, signore?
(sobs)
(sospira)
Course not.
Giusto.
Out of interest...
Per curiosità...
What would happen if I wasn't of sufficient...
Cosa succederebbe se la mia potenza non fosse...
...power...
...abbastanza...
...to pass through the portal?
...da attraversare il portale?
Oh, well in that case, sir, I would tear your flesh from your body and, uh...
Ah, beh, in quel caso signore le strapperei la carne dalle ossa e, hm...
Render your bones down to serve as my soup.
Le frantumerei le ossa fino a ridurle in poltiglia.
Good!
Ah, bene!
Good, good, good.
Bene, bene, bene.
Right.
Ok.